Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Big G, Buggy, and GoGo Smoke performing with Backyard Band at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge, 2013-09-23; 199chippy_1254; Big G smiles at Buggy as he plays the drums while GoGo Smoke plays timbales to the right during a Backyard Band show. Fans is visible in the background.
  - Steve Francis at a Backyard Band show at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge, 2013-09-23; 199chippy_1255; Steve Francis dances at a Backyard Band show. In the background are other fans. To the left a person plays a set of congas.
  - Three people pose for a Mr. G style photo, 2013-09-23; 199chippy_1256; Three people pose for a photograph in front of a painted backdrop featuring a bottle of liquor. The people are dressed for the club. The photographer is likely Mr. G.
  - Backyard Band performing at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge, 2013-09-23; 199chippy_1257; Fans surrounds Backyard Band as they perform at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge. A drums, congas, and keys are all visible.
  - Kacey Williams performing with BLACK ALLEY at the 2013 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2013-09-23; 199chippy_1258; Kacey Williams holds and microphone in her right hand and signs while on stage with BLACK ALLEY at the 2013 National Capital Barbecue Battle. Fans is visible in the background.
  - Tim Okamura painting of Lil Boogie and Mz Laydee at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1239; Opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura. The painting depicts Lil Boogie (left) and Mz Laydee (right).
  - Chip Py with Tim Okamura painting of Lil Boogie and Mz Laydee at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1240; Chip Py poses with half of a painting depicting Lil Boogie and Mz Laydee (right) on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Tim Okamura painting of Lil Boogie at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1241; Opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura. The painting depicts Lil Boogie playing congas.
  - Lil Boogie viewing a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1242; Lil Boogie viewing a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura. A person has their arm around Lil Boogie and supports her arm, she smiles at the painting. The painting depicts Lil Boogie playing congas.
  - Lil Boogie posing with a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1243; Lil Boogie poses in front of a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee posing with a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1244; Mz Laydee poses with her arms crossed in front of a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee next to a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1245; Mz Laydee stand to the left and admires a painting of herself and Lil Boogie on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee posing with a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1246; Mz Laydee poses and smiles in front of a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee posing with a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1247; Mz Laydee poses and smiles in front of a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee viewing a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1248; Mz Laydee stand to the right and smiles as she views a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura. Other attendees surround her.
  - Tim Okamura and Mz Laydee at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1249; Tim Okamura and Mz Laydee stand together in front of a painting of Mz Laydee and Lil Boogie on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee posing with a Tim Okamura painting of herself at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1250; Mz Laydee poses with her arms crossed in front of a painting of herself on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Mz Laydee, Tim Okamura, and Tim Conlon at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1251; From left to right Tim Conlon, Mz Laydee, and Tim Okamura stand together in front of a painting of Mz Laydee and Lil Boogie on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura and Tim Conlon. Tim Okamura makes a peace sign with his left hand.
  - Mz Laydee and Killa Cal with a Tim Okamura painting at the Joan Hisaoka Healing Arts Gallery, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1252; Mz Laydee and her husband Killa Cal pose in front of a painting of Mz Laydee and Lil Boogie on opening night of the Depicted/Connected: Paintings by Tim Okamura.
  - Backyard Band performing at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge, 2013-09-27; 199chippy_1253; Fans surrounds Backyard Band as they perform at Aqua Nightclub and Lounge. A drums, congas, and keys are all visible.
  - BLACK ALLEY performing at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1307; BLACK ALLEY performs on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. From left to right Bo Beedy on percussion, Champ on electric guitar, Animal on drums, Kacey Williams on vocals, Josh on Bass on bass, and Hope Udobi on keyboard.
  - BLACK ALLEY performing at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1308; BLACK ALLEY performs on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. From left to right Champ on electric guitar, Animal on drums, Kacey Williams on vocals, and Josh on Bass on bass.
  - Kacey Williams performs with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1309; Kacey Williams sings with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Kacey Williams performs with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1310; Kacey Williams smiles wide during her performance with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Champ performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1311; Champ wears sunglasses while playing lead electric guitar for BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Champ, Kacey Williams, and Josh on Bass performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1312; Kacey Williams leans back while singing with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. In the background from left to right are Champ on electric guitar, Josh on Bass on bass, and Hope Udobi on keyboard.
  - Champ, Kacey Williams, and Josh on Bass performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1313; Kacey Williams leans back while singing with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. In the background from left to right are Champ on electric guitar, Josh on Bass on bass, and Hope Udobi on keyboard.
  - Kacey Williams, Champ, and Hope Udobi perform with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1314; Kacey Williams and Champ take center stage singing and playing electric guitar with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. Hope Udobi can be seen on the keyboard in the background.
  - BLACK ALLEY performing at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1315; From right to left Champ on electric guitar, Kacey Williams on vocals, and Josh on Bass on bass perform as BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Kacey Williams and Josh on Bass performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1316; Kacey Williams sings while Josh on Bass plays the bass guitar during their performance with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Kacey Williams and Josh on Bass performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1317; From left to right Champ, Josh on Bass, and Kacey Williams perform as BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Kacey Williams center stage with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1318; Kacey Williams sings with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage.
  - Champ, Kacey Williams, and Josh on Bass performing with BLACK ALLEY at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1319; Champ plays the electric guitar behind his head in a feat of guitar showmanship during his performance with BLACK ALLEY on the Kennedy Center's Millennium Stage. Kacey Williams and Josh on Bass can be seen in the background.
  - BLACK ALLEY selling merchandise at the Kennedy Center, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1320; (From right to left) Danny, Josh, Eric, Mack, (sitting right to left) Kacey, and Hope. BLACK ALLEY waits at their merchandise table to sell CD and handout business cards.
  - Tyson Mack, Kacey Williams, Bo Beedy, and Champ of BLACK ALLEY performing at Bar 7, 2013-10-03; 199chippy_1321; From left to right Tyson Mack on keys, Casey Williams on vocals, Bo Beedy on percussion, and Champ on electric guitar perform with BLACK ALLEY at Bar 7..
  - Doug Crowley backstage at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1523; Doug Crowley tunes his electric bass guitar backstage at the Howard Theatre prior to performing with Chuck Brown Band. He is wearing a blue suit. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Band performing at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1524; Unknown band likely performing as the opener at the Howard Theatre. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - KK backstage at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1525; KK pauses for a photo backstage at the Howard Theatre. Greg Boyer and Brad Clements can be seen warming up in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Roy Ayers, Elijah Balbed, and Brad Clements performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1526; Roy Ayers plays the mallets, during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Elijah Balbed and Brad Clements play tenor saxophone and trumpet in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Roy Ayers, Elijah Balbed, and Brad Clements performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1527; Roy Ayers plays the mallets, during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Elijah Balbed and Brad Clements play tenor saxophone and trumpet in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1528; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go plays guitar while singing during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Sweet Cherie plays the keyboard and sings in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1529; Ms Kim points the microphone towards the audience during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Greg Boyer play guitar and trombone in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Ms Kim and KK perform with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1530; Ms Kim and KK sing together into a microphone during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Doug Crowley plays guitar in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1531; Chuck Brown Band performs at the Howard Theatre to celebrate the life of Chuck Brown. Ms Kim can be seen playing the timbales while KK watches. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Doug can be seen in the background playing their instruments. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1532; Chuck Brown Band performs at the Howard Theatre to celebrate the life of Chuck Brown. Ms Kim can be seen playing the timbales while KK watches. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Doug can be seen in the background playing their instruments. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1533; KK holds her drink and points the mic to a fan who reaches out and sings into it. She is performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go is singing, while fans dance and sing in the background. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - KK and Raheem DeVaughn performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1534; Raheem DeVaughn joins Chuck Brown Band on stage at the Howard Theatre. KK raises her drink and the microphone to the audience. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Killa Cal performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1535; Killa Cal rapping as he joins Chuck Brown Band on stage at the Howard Theatre. This event was themed 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown'.
  - Chuck Brown Band's set list for Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1536; This image shows the 24 song set list for the headlining Chuck Brown band for the 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown' themed event at the Howard Theatre.
  - Sweet Cherie with feet in ice backstage at Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1537; Sweet Cherie soaks her feet in ice backstage at the Howard Theatre after her performance with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown Band's set list for Howard Theatre, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1538; This image shows the 24 song set list for the headlining Chuck Brown band for the 'TWO YEARS, NO TEARS: Celebrate the Legacy of Chuck Brown' themed event at the Howard Theatre.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-05-16; 199chippy_1539; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Construction workers can be seen in the background. Ladders. Buckets. And other construction equipment can be seen around the site.
  - Kacey Williams and Josh on Bass performing at Seat Pleasant Day, 2014-05-18; 199chippy_1508; From left to right Kacey Williams and Josh on Bass perform with BLACK ALLEY at Seat Pleasant Day. Kacey kicks her left foot in the air. Josh on Bass hold a guitar.
  - Kacey Williams of BLACK ALLEY performing at Seat Pleasant Day, 2014-05-18; 199chippy_1509; Kacey Williams of BLACK ALLEY performing. Kacey holds the microphone in her right hand. Kacey looks to her left.
  - HouseWives of Benning Road advertisement, 2014-05-18; 199chippy_1510; Flier for the HouseWives of Benning Road.
  - Kacey Williams and Ant of BLACK ALLEY performing at Bar 7, 2014-05-18; 199chippy_1511; Kacey Williams and Ant of BLACK ALLEY performing at Bar 7. Kacey is holding a microphone. Ant is playing the guitar.
  - Penny 'Chinchilla' Braxton on set at Chuck Brown's video shoot for A Beautiful Life, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1495; Penny 'Chinchilla' Braxton holding a sign and posing for the camera.
  - Whiteboy and Tom Goldfogle at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1496; Tom Goldfogle and Whiteboy talk during the video shoot for A Beautiful Life.
  - Kevin Jones on set at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1497; Kevin Jones points at camera. He wears a Go-Go themed t-shirt.
  - Tom Goldfogle, Sweet Cherie and Wiley Brown at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1498; Tom Goldfogle (left) talks with Sweet Cherie (right). Wiley Brown stands in the foreground of the photograph wearing a hat.
  - Wiley Brown at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1499; Wiley Brown looks to his left. Wiley Brown holds boards under his left arm and wears a Chuck Brown themed t-shirt and hat.
  - Nekos and Wiley Brown at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1500; Nekos Brown (left) and Wiley Brown (right) hold poster board under their arms. Nekos is wearing a light colored hat. Wiley is wearing a dark colored hat. There are two camera operators on the far right of the photograph.
  - Big Tony and Tom Goldfogle at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1501; Big Tony (left) talks with Tom Goldfogle (right).
  - Sweet Cherie at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1502; Sweet Cherie holds arms up while holding a poster that reads 'A Beautiful Life '. Sweet Cherie wears a pink bracelet on her right arm.
  - Unidentified participant at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1503; An unidentified person poses with a poster that reads A Beautiful Life.
  - Big Tony at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1504; Big Tony holds a poster that reads A Beautiful Life. Big Tony is wearing a white fedora hat.
  - Video producer Joseph Pattisall and Wiley Brown at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1505; Wiley Brown looks into camera at the A Beautiful Life photo shoot. Wiley Brown is wearing a black fedora hat.
  - Tom Goldfogle, Killa Cal and DJ Blakberri at the A Beautiful Life video shoot, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1506; From left to right Tom Goldfogle, Killa Cal and DJ Blakberri on the set of Chuck Brown's video A Beautiful Life.
  - Kacey Williams going on stage at Seat Pleasant Day, 2014-08-09; 199chippy_1507; Kacey Williams of BLACK ALLEY walking on stage to perform for Seat Pleasant Day. Kacey Williams looks to her left. People are standing and sitting in the background.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1540; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. A Construction worker can be seen in the background piecing together parts of a mural. A sample image of the a mural is pinned to the ground.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1541; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. A Construction worker can be seen in the background piecing together parts of a mural. A sample image of the a mural lay on the ground.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1542; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Construction workers piece together parts of murals. Ladders. Buckets. And other construction equipment can be seen around the site.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1543; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. A Construction worker can be seen piecing together parts of a mural. Ladders. Buckets. And other construction equipment can be seen around the site. The murals show various images of Chuck Brown.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1544; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Two Construction workers can be seen piecing together parts of a mural. Construction equipment can be seen around the site. The murals show various images of Chuck Brown.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1545; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. A Construction worker can be seen piecing together parts of a mural. Construction equipment can be seen around the site.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1546; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. There is a sculpture covered in material sitting on a platform that reads 'Chuck Brown Memorial Park'. Construction equipment can be seen around the site.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1547; The Chuck Brown Memorial Park government authorized Construction sign and public notice. The posting details that the memorial is being erected under then Mayor Vincent C. Gray.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1548; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt and a worker can be seen operating a excavator with Post driver attachment. Other construction workers and equipment can be seen around the site.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1549; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt and a worker can be seen operating a excavator with Post driver attachment. Other construction workers are laying a foundation within a trench.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1550; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt and construction workers can be seen digging a trench.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1551; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt and a worker can be seen operating a excavator with Post driver attachment. Other construction workers are in the image.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1552; The Chuck Brown Memorial Park government authorized Construction sign and public notice. The posting details that the memorial and park was designed by Marshall Moya Design (architecture firm).
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1553; A construction worker sits in his pickup truck. He's wearing sunglasses, a baseball cap, and is smoking a cigarette.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1554; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt. There is various equipment, machinery, and construction workers on the site. The Langdon Park East Recreation Center can be seen in the background.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1555; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. The Construction site is all dirt. Construction workers can seen and a set of concrete stairs are visible.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1556; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Construction workers are laying barriers to prepare to pour concrete. Various construction equipment and machinery are visible.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1557; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Construction workers are laying barriers to prepare to pour concrete. Various construction equipment is visible.
  - Construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park, 2014-08-13; 199chippy_1558; Progress photograph of the construction of Chuck Brown Memorial Park. Construction workers are laying barriers to prepare to pour concrete. A Schwing concrete pump (machine) and various construction equipment and machines are visible.